It's cute.
可愛いですね
Are you showing me?
見せてんの?
What is it?
何がですか?
何がですかって
tits.
おっぱい
I'm not showing it.
見せてないんですよ
I can see your breasts.
おっぱい見えてるよ
Did you notice?
気づいてた?
I can't help it now.
今、仕方ないからね
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっと色々聞いてもいい?
yes.
はい
How old are you now?
今何歳?
I'm already 18 years old and will soon be 19.
もう18歳で、もうすぐ19歳になります
Oh, soon?
あら、もうすぐ?
yes.
はい
Is your birthday coming up?
誕生日近いの?
yes.
はい
Congratulations.
おめでとう
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
a little bit...
ちょっと...
I will.
するよね
yes.
はい
I can see your amazing breasts though.
すごいおっぱい見えてるけど
Are you showing me?
見せてくれてんの?
That's not the case.
そういうわけじゃなくて
yes.
はい
nice.
いいね
I got a reply.
返事が入った
I see.
そっか
What are you doing now?
今何してるの?
What do you usually do?
普段は?
student?
学生?
yes.
はい
While a student, I worked part-time and had a hobby.
学生しながら、アルバイトと趣味と
hobby?
趣味?
Part-time job and hobby.
アルバイトと趣味
Be a student.
学生して
University?
大学?
yes.
はい
University.
大学
I'm here.
います
Are you a first year student?
1年生なの?
yes.
はい
What did you study?
何勉強したの?
what?
何?
literature.
文学
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's a liberal arts field.
文系なんだね
yes.
はい
It's a liberal arts field.
文系です
nice.
いいね
Are you used to it?
慣れました?
As for school.
学校は
yes.
はい
Somewhat.
多少は
How much?
多少は?
Where are you from?
出身はどこなの?
I am originally from Hokkaido.
出身は、北海道です
oh!
おー!
There are a lot of really cute kids from Hokkaido.
北海道の子ってすごい可愛い子多いね
Which side?
どの辺なの?
Hokkaido.
北海道
Well, I'm Rie.
え っと、リエです
That's it.
あれだね
Wait, you live in the countryside?
ちょっと、田舎の方?
I'm sorry if I call it rural.
田舎って言ったらちょっと申し訳ないけど
It's the countryside.
田舎です
I've heard of it.
聞いたことある
It's kind of delicious, isn't it?
なんか美味しいよね
Are shrimp delicious?
海老とか美味しい?
yes.
はい
I really like shrimp because it's shrimp.
海老だからめちゃくちゃ好きなんですよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
That's nice.
いいな
Hokkaido.
北海道
Ah, so I just had a situation.
あ、じゃあ状況したばっかりなんだ
yes.
はい
Well, what do you do part-time?
えー、アルバイトは何してるの?
Well, soba.
え っと、蕎麦
This is a soba restaurant.
蕎麦屋です
Soba restaurant?
蕎麦屋?
yes.
はい
Eh, are you making soba?
えー、蕎麦作ってる?
Oh, no.
あ、違う
I'll just put it out.
私は出すだけですよ
I wouldn't do something like that though.
そんな、こんなやったりしないですけど
Oh, are you going to serve the soba you made?
あ、作られた蕎麦を出すの?
yes.
はい
supply?
提供?
Eh, I want to go.
えー、行きたい
yes.
はい
Well, yes.
まあ、はい
So, are you just exposing your breasts and serving soba noodles?
で、そのままおっぱい出して、蕎麦出してるの?
No, it actually looks like this kind of shrimp.
いや、ちゃんともうこんな海老みたいな
Ah, okay?
あ、ちゃんとね?
yes.
はい
By the way, do you have any other part-time jobs?
そこはね、他なんかしてるアルバイトは?
Well, my hobbies include bands, so...
え っと、趣味がバンドとかなんで、
One-off part-time jobs for people like live staff and festivals.
ライブスタッフみたいなフェスみたいなやつの単発バイトとかたま
I'm doing it.
に やってます
Ah, I love music.
あ、音楽が好きなんだ
Live shows.
ライブとか
Eh, nice.
えー、いいね
That's a good job.
いい仕事だね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you have any dreams?
なんか夢とかある?
My dream is to form a band with my friends and have a debut.
夢は、友達とバンド組んでテビューすることです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
yes.
はい
She's a girl in a band.
バンド女子なんだね
Eh, like a girl band?
えー、ガールズバンド的な?
yes.
はい
Are there any bands you're aiming for?
目標にしてるバンドとかあります?
The goal is to kill the dead.
目標は、死者をです
That's good.
いいよね
That's right.
そうなんだ
What are you doing?
何やってるの?
A guitar?
ギターとか?
vocal.
ボーカル
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It looks like you can sing it.
歌うまそうだもんね
Can I go see the live performance?
ライブ見に行っていい?
Yes, please.
はい、ぜひ
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Where are you doing it?
どこでやってるの?
We rent a live house in Shibuya and perform occasionally.
渋谷のライブハウスを借りて、たまにやってます
It's pretty serious.
結構ガチだね
It's true.
ガチです
That's serious.
ガチだね
If you walk around Shibuya, you'll probably get a lot of people talking to you.
渋谷なんて歩いてたらさ、結構声かけとかされるでしょ
From the man.
男のところから
It's like picking up girls.
ナンパみたいなの
Well, sometimes.
まあ、たまに
I think you'll be really impressed.
めっちゃされると思うよ
It's cute.
可愛いし
What are you going to do about that?
それ、スースーどうする?
Are you following me?
ついていくの?
No, you won't go.
いや、行かないでしょ
Don't you want to go?
行かない?
yes.
はい
real?
ほんと?
yes.
はい
Didn't you hear about the number of people with experience?
経験人数とか聞いたじゃない?
How many people?
何人くらい?
1 person.
1人です
Seriously?
マジで?
Are you that much of a man?
そんなに、男れ?
yes.
はい
Is there only one person?
1人しかないの?
No.
ないです
picture?
え?
Really?
ほんとに?
yes.
はい
Well, you're young.
まあ、若いしね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Wouldn't you like to experience it?
経験してみたいんじゃない?
How about an old man's cock?
なんか、おじさんのチンポとか、どう?
Isn't that why you came?
だから来てくれたんじゃない?
yes.
はい
Are you not used to seeing dick?
あんま、チンチン見慣れてない?
Maybe.
もしかして
Not much.
あんまり
real?
ほんと?
A cock that looks a bit like a capelin.
ちょっと、シシャモみたいなチンポ
Shishamo.
シシャモね
It's shishamo.
シシャモだ
The faceless shishamo is famous.
無顔のシシャモが有名ですからね、
Hokkaido.
北海道
It's shishamo.
シシャモだ
Shishamo?
シシャモ?
this.
これ
Shishamo.
シシャモ
I think it's a little thicker than Shishamo.
シシャモよりちょっと、太めだと思う
It's a spiny lobster.
イセエビだ
Spiny lobster.
イセエビ
Spiny shrimp?
イセエビ?
Oh, that's so admirable.
あ、そんなに立派だよ
Well, her breasts are really visible.
てか、ほんとにおっぱい丸見えなんですね
Are you in a band?
バンドしてるの?
yes.
はい
nice.
いいね
Your smile is cute.
笑顔かわいいね
I have dimples.
エクボがあるんですよ
Oh, that's true.
あ、ほんとだ
I have dimples.
エクボがある
cute.
かわいい
If this were a band, it would definitely be popular.
これ、バンドだったら絶対人気出るじゃん
If only it had a cute vocal.
かわいいボーカルだったら
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yay!
やったー
When will you make your debut?
デビューはいつとかする?
It hasn't been decided yet.
まだ決まってないです
Haven't you decided yet?
まだ 決まってないの?
Can I go to a live show?
ちょっとライブ行ってもいいかな?
please.
ぜひ
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
I want you to see it.
見てほしい
Seriously?
マジで?
That's not true.
そんなことないんだよ
picture?
え?
this is?
これは?
How many centimeters?
何 センチぐらい?
Kurukuju...about 2 or 3.
くるくじゅう...2、3くらい
This is work.
これ、仕事だろ
Huh?
あれ?
I can only see double.
二重ぐらいしか見えない
Isn't it too thin?
細すぎない?
a little bit.
ちょっと
The situation is too bad.
状況すぎなんで
You have it.
持ってるのね
yes.
はい
buckwheat.
そば
buckwheat?
そば?
What menu for soba?
そばへの何のメニュー?
Soba, um, tempura soba.
そばや、あの、天ぷらそば
Ah, shrimp after all.
ああ、やっぱエビ
shrimp.
エビ
I like shrimp though.
エビ好きだけど
shrimp.
エビ
nice.
いいね
Why are you dressed like this?
なんでこんな格好してるの?
I can really see it though.
めっちゃ見えてるけど
It's not on purpose.
わざとじゃないんですよ
picture?
え?
by chance?
たまたま?
yes.
はい
What, you got wrapped up by the clerk?
なに、店員に包まれたの?
this.
これ
No, no.
いやいや
Eh, because if something like this comes, I'm sure I'll get snapped.
え、だってこんなの来たら絶対ナップされちゃうじゃん
Get your size and order it online.
サイズにしちゃって通販で
Ah, I bought it online.
あ、通販で買ったんだね
yes.
はい
Yes, there is.
あるあるだ
Yeah.
うん
But hey...
でもちょっと...
It really suits you.
やっぱ似合ってる
It's cute.
かわいいね
Is it okay to have 2 Yokojis who have experienced life?
経験人生2人の横じさんでいいの?
It's a simple question though.
素朴な疑問なんだけど
difficult.
難しい
picture?
え?
difficult?
難しい?
difficult.
難しい
The chopsticks are so beautiful.
お箸めっちゃ綺麗
It's smooth, just a little.
すべすべやん、ちょっと
Mr. Young.
若さん
Mr. Young?
若さん?
Like an old man or a young man.
じいさん、お若さんみたいな
Is anyone doing it?
誰もやってるか?
Your pants are cute.
パンツかわいいね
It has a ribbon.
リボンついてる
Huge ribbon.
でかいリボン
Breasts G cup.
おっぱいGカップ
G cup?
Gカップ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Everyone will see your boobs.
みんな見てくるでしょ、おっぱい
To be seen or not to be seen?
見られるか見られないか?
Can be seen.
見られる
difficult.
難しい
You'll be seen wearing this outfit.
この服着てたら見られるでしょ
Size mistake.
サイズミス
Is it a size mistake?
サイズミスか
How do you usually say this?
普段はこれどう言うの?
Up to around here.
ここら辺まで
Is this the perfect fit?
これでピッタリするやつ?
yes.
そう
Is this OK?
これでもOK?
difficult.
難しい
Please do me a favor.
お願いにして
Ass request.
お尻のお願い
Listen to my butt's wishes.
お尻のお願い聞いて
it hurts?
痛い?
OK
The material is a bit old so I have to get it across.
ネタがちょっと古いから通じないといけない
I understand.
わかるよ
Do you understand?
わかる?
Yeah.
うん
It's amazing on the neck.
首ですごいね
A while ago, a little while ago.
昔、ちょっと
Absolutely, absolutely.
絶対絶対
You're well trained.
鍛えられてるね
The underwear is really cute though.
下着めっちゃかわいいんだけど
I'll see you for the last time.
最後に目見ちゃうね
oh dear.
まあ
Because it's a boy.
男の子なんで
You understand boys very well.
男の子のことよく理解してるね
They definitely said that in class.
クラスでも絶対言われたでしょ
Big boobs.
おっぱいでかい
No, I don't know.
いやいや、わかんない
It becomes a hot topic in university classes.
大学のクラスで話題になる
This is dangerous even if you're wearing a school uniform.
学生服着ててもこれはやばいわ
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
direct?
直接?
No?
ダメ?
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
Show me your child's chenpo later.
後でお子さんのチェンポ見せてあげて
Publication conditions.
公開条件
It's already taken off.
もう外してるじゃん
good?
いい?
2 seconds, just 2 seconds.
2秒、2秒だけ
Just 2 seconds.
2秒だけ
good.
いい
long.
長い
Uncle, you've got a lot of time to spare.
おじさんね、ちょっとね、時間の覚悟すごいですね
1 second is about 1 year.
1秒が1年くらい
amazing.
すごい
Can I have a look at this for about a year?
1年くらいこれちょっと見せてもらっていい?
I don't know.
わかんない
keep it up.
がんばれ
It's embarrassing, really.
恥ずかしいよ、ほんとに
Is it really embarrassing?
ほんと恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Uncle, hold me in your arms like this.
おじさん、こうやって手で抱っこしといて
kind.
優しい
You're kind, aren't you?
優しいでしょ?
Sometimes I open my fingers like this.
たまにこうやって指開くけど
It feels good for about 2 years.
2年くらい、気持ちいいよ
Is it really okay to step on it for about a year?
1年くらい、ほんとに踏んでいってもいい?
real?
ほんと?
good?
いい?
Okay?
いいか?
Something too.
なんかも
Maybe.
かもしれない
Well, certainly.
まあ、確かにね
If we were together, I wouldn't know anymore.
一緒だったらもうわかんないよね
Yeah.
うん
kind.
優しい
She's a goddess, I guess.
女神だね、ちょっとね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
I'm being watched a lot.
めっちゃ見られてる
I can't help it, it's beautiful.
しょうがないよ、綺麗なんだから
Does it feel good to drink?
飲められるの、気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Why is it cute?
なんでかわいいの?
Is there such a thing as cute?
かわいいとかある?
Yes, your belly button is cute.
あるよ、おへそかわいい
Keep your head down, it might be a problem.
おへそってね、せいかも
Maybe it's a good thing.
いいせいかもしれない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What's below?
下は?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Are you embarrassed about the top too?
上も恥ずかしい?
Well, if it's in the middle.
じゃあ中間だったら
Okay.
いいよ
shame
恥
That's embarrassing.
ず かしい
What's below?
下は?
Are you embarrassed below?
下は恥ずかしい?
But, it's kind of damp.
でも さ、だいぶなんか湿ってるんだけど
Uncle, is this a misunderstanding?
おじさん、これ勘違いか?
I feel like it's quite damp.
だいぶ湿ってる気がするんだけど
misunderstanding.
勘違い
Is that a misunderstanding? Is that so?
勘違いか、そっかそっか
Well, I haven't seen it yet, so can I check?
じゃあちょっと、見ないから確認してもいい?
No?
ダメ?
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
It's okay if you say you're embarrassed.
恥ずかしいって言ったら大丈夫
I can't see it, I can't see it.
見えてない、見えてない
I can't see it, it's okay.
見えてない、大丈夫
Uncle, are you feeling okay?
おじさん、気持ちいいかな?
Not seen.
見られてない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I say it's embarrassing.
恥 ず か しいって言っちゃう
This clicking sound.
このくちくち音
Eh, no way.
えー、やば
No?
やだ?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
close?
近い?
Eh, no way.
えー、やば
No?
やだ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
So cute, so cute.
めっちゃ可愛い、めっちゃ可愛い
Uncle gets really excited.
おじさんはすごい興奮する
Yeah, but it's super wet though.
え、 でもさ、超濡れてるけどさ、
Will this get my pants dirty?
これパンツ汚れちゃうよ?
Just stay like this.
このままじゃ
Well, I have no choice but to take it off.
じゃ、脱ぐしかないじゃん
Well, if I get my pants dirty, I won't be able to go home.
あれ、パンツ汚したらさ、帰れなくなっちゃう
I won't be able to go home with a brain panel.
脳パネ帰れなくなっちゃうよ
The brain panel is more embarrassing.
脳パネのほうが恥ずかしいじゃん
Well, I can't go home even if I'm dirty.
えー、汚れても帰れないよ
I can't go home.
帰れないじゃん
It's okay, uncle will clean it up later.
おじさんは後で汚すから大丈夫
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Show it to your uncle.
お じさんに見せて
A lifelong wish.
一生のお願い
lifetime?
一 生?
A lifelong wish.
一生のお願い
Just a little bit.
ちょっと だけだよ
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Good thing my pants weren't dirty.
よかった、パンツ汚れてなかった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Sorry, uncle.
ごめんね、おじさん
I won't do anything unpleasant.
嫌なことはしないから
Uncle, I'll put this on and go home.
ちゃんとおじさん、これ被って帰るから
Please open your uncle's pants.
おじさんのパンツ開けてください
TRUE?
本当?
Please open your pants if you have to wash them for about 3 days.
3日くらい洗ってねば、パンツ開けてください
I really hate it.
めっちゃ嫌だ
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
It's cute.
可愛いよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Don't wear anything weird.
変なのつけないで
If it stays wet, it won't feel good,
濡れたままだったら気持ち悪いから、
I have to clean it up.
きれいにしなきゃ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Because it doesn't feel bad.
気持ち悪くないから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Uncle is okay too.
おじも大丈夫
Show me, please.
見せて、お願い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You said you'd show me a little bit.
ちょっと見せてくれるって言ったじゃん
I just showed you.
今見せたの
I can't show it yet.
まだ見せない
My uncle, I can't see him because he's Mork.
おじにね、モークだから見えない
Then you won't be able to see it forever.
じゃあずっと見えないじゃん
Legs, can you ride here for a moment?
足さ、ちょっとここ乗っけられる?
please.
お願い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
A lifelong wish, a lifelong wish.
一生のお願い、一生のお願い
I've already used my lifelong wish.
一生のお願い、もう使ったよ
My uncle is about 7th grade.
おじ7小くらいだから
Just go up one level.
一つだけ上に上がって
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Are you okay with your posture?
大丈夫かな、体勢
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいなの
I really need 2 pieces please.
本当に2小お願いし
There's 5 more left.
あと5小残ってるじゃん
I found out.
バレた
I can use 3 small pieces, please.
3小使っていいからお願い
I have two more to finish.
あと2小終わるよ
I think I'll save 2nd grade for urgent matters.
2小は緊急事項にちょっと取っとこうかな
This is it...
これさ、こっからさ...
No, no, my uncle is hiding it.
違う違う、おじこれ隠してるから
Because I'm hiding my identity.
お じ隠してるから
Get your hand out of here.
こっちの手、こっから出して
Let's take this out, let's take this out.
これ出して、こっち出すじゃん
Hey, open up here a little bit.
ちょっとさ、ここちょっと開いて
It's really impossible because it's embarrassing.
それは恥ずかしいから本当に無理
amazing.
すごい
Well then, you can use the 11th grade of the 2nd grade as an emergency.
じゃあ緊急の2小の11小使っていいから
It's super urgent.
超緊急じゃん
It's super urgent so I'd like to take a look.
超緊急だからちょっと見たいの
It's 1 small.
1小だよ
I want to open it.
開いてみたいんだよ
I want to open this.
開いてみたいのこれ
I'm not saying it's okay.
いいって言ってない
Sorry, my uncle's hands are shaking too much.
ごめん、おじ手揺れすぎてそう
It's shaking too much.
揺れすぎだよ
My hands are shaking so much that I can't see.
ちょっと手揺れすぎて見えない
It's okay because my uncle is a bit blind.
おじちょっと盲目だから大丈夫
Blind?
盲目?
Open it like this.
開いてこういうふうに
Put your finger here.
ここに指入って
Stretch out your hand.
手伸ばして
Show me your hands.
手に見せて
Just a little bit, really.
本当にちょっとだけね
Haven't you seen too much?
見すぎじゃない?
I was just looking from the left.
さっき左から見てたから
I'm looking from the right now.
今ちょっと右から見てる
It's so beautiful whether you look at it from the right or the left.
右から見ても左から見てもめちゃくちゃきれいだから
Ah, not yet.
あ、まだまだ
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
It's not over yet.
まだ終わってない
Is it still there?
まだあんの?
I can't see my uncle yet.
おじまだ全然見えてない
Ah, I was getting a little carried away.
あ、もうちょっとだいぶわたきしてたから
I can't see it.
見えてない
Even though there wasn't so much.
こんなに無かったのに
Week after week.
一周一周一周
It's finished.
終わったよ
Is it over?
終わっちゃったの?
It's wet, isn't it?
濡れてるよね
It's like this.
こんな感じ
It's not a feeling.
気持ちじゃないよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
It's really amazing.
やっぱすごい
You have such a beautiful pussy and ass.
すごいきれいなおまんまお尻でしょ
narrow?
狭い?
narrow.
狭い
Not really like that.
あんまりそういうの
Didn't your ex-boyfriend call you small?
元彼に狭いって言われなかった?
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
It's for comparison.
比較対象だよね
Yeah.
うん
Eh, is that so?
えー、そうなの?
yes.
はい
Did it twitch just now?
今ピクって動いた?
You don't have to say that.
そういうの言わなくていい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Please.
どうか
You're lying.
嘘言ってるね
I'm pacing again.
またペースしてる
picture?
え?
I'm pacing again.
またペースしてる
You don't have to show it because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから見せなくていい
picture?
え?
I've been laughing since a while ago.
笑ってるよさっきから
Good picture book.
いい絵本
Was your uncle's dick of the opposite sex?
おじさんのチンコ、異性やった?
Yeah.
うん
I keep complaining while laughing.
笑いながらどんどん文句しまるんだけど
Maybe it's because I'm laughing.
笑ってるからかもしれない
Yeah.
うん
How do you do it then?
その ときはどうやってすんの?
hand?
手?
A dick like that?
そんなチンコ?
Yeah.
うん
hand.
手
Where is that?
それがどこ?
By official name.
正式名称で
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
I don't really understand.
あんまりわかんない
Don't you know?
わか んない?
Well then, let's try it.
じゃあ、やってみよう
Let's try it.
やってみよう
Let's go, let's try.
行ってみよう、やってみよう
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
lobster.
いせえび
lobster?
いせえび?
Seriously?
まじで?
Haven't washed it in 3 days?
3日洗ってない?
It smells like lobster.
いせえびの匂いしてる
Really?
ほんとに?
Yeah.
うん
The serious nature of the competition is a bit of an issue.
競技の深刻はちょっと抜速の対象になりますけど
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it a bad smell?
悪い匂いではない?
Really?
ほんとに?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
If you see me like that.
そんな見られたら
Well, it's cute, so I want to take a look.
えー、だって可愛いからちょっと見たいじゃん
I've always done it manually though.
ずっと手動いてますけど
It's become fun.
楽しくなっちゃった
With my uncle Chinkin?
おじのチンキンと?
It got bigger.
大きくなった
beginning.
初め
lobster.
いせえび
Ise shrimp.
いせえびなんて
Well then, I like shrimp.
じゃあちょっと、えび好きだ
big.
大きい
Is this yellowtail?
これ、ぶり?
Yeah.
うん
Better than that.
と かないより
big?
大きい?
How much?
どれくらい?
ど れくらい?
times.
倍
Double?
倍?
Eh, is your ex-boyfriend like this?
え、もとカレこんなの?
That's not the case though.
そんなことはないけど
I don't know if it's done well.
うまくできてるかわかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Because that part is done well.
そこがうまくできてるから
Please extend it a little.
ちょっと延長お願いします
I can't see your butt completely from above.
お尻が上から丸見えないんだけど
Well then.
じゃあこそ
Can I put it in my pigtails?
おなげで挟んでもいい?
I'll pack it.
詰めてやる
Is this dangerous?
これやばい?
inch?
インチ?
It's a little dirty
ちょっと汚れたらし
Chau.
ちゃ う
Scary, scary, these things are going to change.
怖い怖い、こたち変わっちゃう
It's covered in blood.
血でつれてる
Anything is fine.
なんでもいいんじゃん
Eh, nothing's good.
え、なんでもよくないよ
There is no such thing.
とかない
Ah, I see.
あ、 そうか
Yes, Dow
はい、ダウ
hmm.
ン
In this state, I'm down.
この 状態で、ダウンってして
So cute.
かわいいな
It's super erotic though.
超エロいんだけど
child
こ
Her lips are also licked.
っち のくちくびも舐められる
Climb on top like this.
このまま上に乗っかって
Uncle, I'm starting to want to come in.
おじさん、入れたくなってきちゃった
I want to put it in.
入れたい
Do you want to enter?
入れたい?
No.
ダメ
What, no?
え、ダメなの?
Yeah.
うん
I told him it would make me feel better.
それで気分乗ったらいいって言って
What is that?
何それ
Uncle, I wish you could drink a little more seriously.
おじさんね、ちょっと本気で飲めればよいです
So stand up a little.
だからちょっと立てて
Just stand up.
ちょっと立ち上がって
ratio?
比率?
In proportion.
比率して
Also, the old man's face is nice.
で、おじさんの顔またいい
Okay, okay, let's move forward a little.
よいしょ、はい、ちょっと前へ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Oh, wow, I don't like her boobs and her face either.
あ、すごい、おっぱいで顔も嫌なんだけど
What chapter request?
何章のお願い?
Wait, how many chapters are left?
えっと、あと何章残ってたっけ?
That's enough.
もういいや
Until chapter one.
一章まで
One chapter?
一章?
One chapter.
一章
Everything is a bit of a challenge.
ちょっと何事も挑戦というか
It's really warm though.
すっごいあったかいんだけど
Is it in?
入ってる?
It's in.
入ってる
amazing.
すごい
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Is this okay?
これ大丈夫かな?
Can you put it on without sleeping?
寝てないで、つける?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, I'm getting wet again.
すごい、また濡れてきてる
Yeah.
うん
I'm really in trouble.
すごい困る
I can't even see your face.
顔も見とけないんだけど
Can't you fall anymore?
もう 落ちちゃダメ?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
It's a little dirty.
ちょっとしみやで
No.
ダメ
And I can't even see my uncle's face.
そして、おじさんの顔もできない
Is it okay?
ダメかい?
Yeah.
うん
a little bit.
ちょっと
already.
もう
picture?
え?
But, no.
でもさ、ダメさ
Look at this, look at this.
これ見て、これ見て
My sperm is buzzing.
精子ブグブグいってる
That's amazing sperm.
すごい精子かい
I might not be sorry.
めんないかもしれない
It's getting even more slimy.
さらにぬるぬるになってる
I put it away even more after I said I was going to sleep.
寝そうって言ってからさらにしまったんだけど
I ate so much that I collapsed.
食べすぎて谷巻いちゃった
My legs are covered in sperm.
精子で足かかってる
I spilled a lot of sperm.
めっちゃ精子かけちゃった
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
ごめんね、おっしゃってる
Let's see, Abite.
しょーわーでね、あびて
It's beautiful, isn't it?
きれいでしょ
Sorry, I was just here.
ごめんね、しょーわーきてた?
I was done.
きれてた
came.
きた
graduate may Ikita is now empty
graduate may Ikita 今はあき
bringing It's dangerous.
bringing やばいわ
I don't ask
お願いしない
in.
で
Ah, she's such a good woman, isn't she?
あ、 お仕方がある良い女ってやつだね、
This is it.
これね
I'm wearing two pieces over my shoulders.
肩を2個かけましてるのに
Is this how you want to do it?
こうやってやりたいのかな?
How about not taking pictures with a camera?
カメラで撮らないでどう?
It's smooth.
なめらかーって
Smooth.
なめらか
It'll be smooth.
なめらかーだろうし
It tickled.
すぐった
Damn it, it tickled.
やべて、すぐった
It looks like a pedestal, so it has to have legs.
やっぱ台座っぽいから足とかないといけない
This is bubbles, so this is it.
これ泡泡だから、これ
Because it's foamy, this is it.
泡泡だから、これ
Bubbles.
泡泡
No?
ダメ?
Is there some sort of bubble?
なんか泡泡のところあるのかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Grandpa and bubbles.
おじいちゃんとか泡泡のところ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This, this futon has already been subtracted by 2 minutes.
もうこれ、 この布団も2分引いてる
Because it's a foot.
足だから
I'll have to wash it a little more thoroughly.
ちょっとしっかり洗わないといけないね
oh
お
Mr. Ji, I put it away once again.
じ さん、もう1回しまってきちゃった
real?
ほんと?
Because I added my sage.
マイセージつけちゃったから
You can go, right?
いけるでしょ?
Hey, it's the first time.
ちょっと、最初じゃん
I went back because it was designed.
設計されたから戻った
Can I have it in my butt?
お尻にもらっていい?
good.
いい
a,
あ、
different.
違う
Are you going to do it?
や るの?
No, no.
違う、違う
I was really pushed.
めっちゃ押されちゃった
Even though I had a ticket, I took the trouble to get Wakey's number.
入れがあったのに、 せっかくウェイキーの番号
It's Wakey's number.
ウェイキーの番号だって
Although there was a case,
入れがあったのに、
I wish it meant that.
そんな 意味だったらいいよ